http://www.equinecomfort.com/pages/return-policy

Terms of Use / Privacy Policy
Equine Comfort Products:
Terms & Conditions Of Sale:
Welcome to www.equinecomfort.com and its related sites, which include but are not limited to (the "Sites"). Eurow & O’Reilly Corporation and its brands, including but not limited to (referred to in this document as “ECP”) provides the Sites as a service to our customers. Please review these terms and conditions of use (the “Agreement”) which govern your use of the sites.
By using the Sites you agree to follow and be bound by this Agreement (you, together with ECP are sometimes referred to as the “Parties”). ECP reserves the right to change, update or modify this Agreement at any time without prior notice. As a result, you should review this Agreement every time you use any of the Sites. If you do not agree to the terms of this Agreement, you should not use the Sites.
Contents of the Sites
Unless otherwise stated in this Agreement or elsewhere on the Sites, the Sites, and all materials on the Sites, including images, illustrations, photographs, icons, designs, text, video clips and other materials, and the copyrights, trademarks, trade dress and/or other intellectual property in such materials (collectively, the "Contents") are owned, controlled or licensed by ECP and other trademarks appearing on the Sites are the trademarks of ECP and/or its subsidiaries, affiliates or partners.
The Sites and the Contents are intended solely for personal, non-commercial use. You may download or copy the Contents and other downloadable materials displayed on the Sites for your personal use only. No right, title or interest in any downloaded Content is transferred to you as a result of any such downloading or copying. You may not reproduce (except as noted above), publish, transmit, distribute, display, modify, create derivative works from, sell or exploit in any way any of the Contents or the Sites.
Unless otherwise specified, the Sites and the Contents are intended to promote ECP's products and services available in the United States.
Transactions on the Sites
ECP does not guarantee the availability of the merchandise through the Sites, as stock may vary, and we reserve the right to limit or refuse any order that is placed with us. We may, in our sole discretion, limit or cancel quantities purchased per person, per household or per order. These restrictions may include orders placed by or under the same customer account, the same credit card, and/or orders that use the same billing and/or shipping address. In the event that ECP makes a change to or cancels an order, we will try to notify you by contacting the contact information you provided during the transaction, including your e-mail and/or billing address/phone number. We reserve the right to limit or prohibit orders that, in our sole judgment, appear to be placed by dealers, resellers or distributors. Currently, ECP only accepts orders from and ships to the United States.
Right to Change Sites
ECP reserves the right, at any time, in our sole discretion, to:
Modify, suspend or discontinue the Sites or any service, content, feature or product offered through the Sites, with or without notice;
Charge fees in connection with the use of the Sites;
Modify and/or waive any fees charged in connection with the Sites; and/or
Offer opportunities to some or all users of the Sites.
You agree that ECP shall not be liable to you or to any third party for any modification, suspension or discontinuance of the Site, or any service, content, feature or product offered through the Sites.
User Comments and User Submitted Materials
ECP may allow comments regarding our products and services on the Sites or elsewhere. However, ECP’s company policy does not allow us to accept or to consider any unsolicited materials, including suggestions, creative ideas, plans, product proposals, etc., other than those that have been specifically requested by ECP. We have put this policy in place to avoid any misunderstandings regarding when projects developed by ECP, or its employees, agents, partners or affiliates, might appear to be similar to materials submitted by users. Accordingly, although ECP appreciates hearing from its users and fans, we must ask that you do not send us any creative ideas, suggestions, proposals, plans, or other materials for our business. If, upon our explicit request, you send certain specific submissions (for example, contest entries, customer reviews or photographs) or without a request from us you send creative ideas, suggestions, customer reviews, photographs, proposals, plans, or other materials, whether online, by email, by postal mail, or otherwise (collectively, "Comments"), you agree that ECP may, at any time, without restriction, edit, copy, publish, distribute, translate, and otherwise use in any medium any Comments that you forward to ECP. ECP is and shall be under no obligation (1) to maintain any Comments in confidence; (2) to pay compensation for any Comments; or (3) to respond to any Comments. ECP has the right but not the obligation to monitor and edit or remove any Comments.
You agree that your Comments will not violate any right of any third party, including copyright, trademark, privacy or other personal or proprietary right. You further agree that your Comments will not contain libelous or otherwise unlawful, abusive or obscene material, or contain any computer virus or other malware that could in any way affect the operation of the Sites. You are not permitted to use a false e-mail address, pretend to be someone other than yourself or assume a false identity, or otherwise mislead ECP or third parties as to the origin of any Comments. You are solely responsible for any Comments you make and their accuracy. ECP takes no responsibility and assumes no liability for any Comments posted by your or any third party.
Submitting Personal Information to ECP
This Agreement incorporates the ECP Privacy Policy (the “Privacy Policy”), in the link located in the footer of the Sites, by reference. Any personal information you submit to or through any of the Sites or through any other method is governed by its terms.
Product Description and Information
The prices displayed on the Sites are quoted in U.S. Dollars.
Products available through the Sites may have limited quantities and are subject to return or exchange only through the Sites according to the applicable return policy. In addition, some products displayed on the Sites are available exclusively online.
Errors, Inaccuracies, and Omissions
Information on the sites may contain typographical errors, inaccuracies, or omissions that may relate to product descriptions, promotions, pricings, offers and availability. ECP reserves the right to correct any such errors, inaccuracies or omissions and to change or update any information on the sites or cancel any orders if at any time, without any prior notice, including after you have submitted an order through the Sites or otherwise.
Colors
ECP has endeavored to accurately display the colors of our products on our sites. However, we cannot guarantee that our products will appear as they do on our Sites as displayed on your monitor or any other device with which you view the sites.
Links to Third Party Sites
The Sites may contain links to other websites (the “Linked Sites”) that are not under the control of ECP. ECP is not responsible for the content, security, availability, accuracy or practices of the Linked Sites and expressly disclaims any responsibility for malware, worms, time bombs, bots, or any other harmful or deleterious programs or materials in said links or Linked Sites. The user assumes all risk and responsibility if he or she clicks on a link on the Sites that leads the user away from the Sites.
Accordingly, ECP has no responsibility for the linked Web sites nor does linking constitute an endorsement of any Linked Sites unless otherwise stated in writing. Links are provided solely for the convenience and information of the Sites' users.
Security; No Warranties
ECP ENDEAVORS TO SECURE ITS SITES BY UTILIZING COMMERCIALLY REASONABLE SECURITY PRACTICES, BUT IT CANNOT GUARANTEE THAT ITS SERVICES WILL BE ERROR-FREE OR COMPLETELY SECURE.  ECP WILL ATTEMPT TO PROVIDE THE SITES WITHOUT INTERRUPTION, BUT THE SITES AND ALL INFORMATION, CONTENT, MATERIALS, PRODUCTS (INCLUDING SOFTWARE) AND OTHER SERVICES INCLUDED ON OR OTHERWISE MADE AVAILABLE TO YOU THROUGH THE SITES ARE PROVIDED BY ECP ON AN "AS IS" AND "AS AVAILABLE" BASIS, UNLESS OTHERWISE SPECIFIED IN WRITING. ECP DOES NOT GUARANTEE THAT YOU WILL BE ABLE TO ACCESS THE SITES AT ANY TIME OF YOUR CHOOSING.
TO THE FULLEST EXTENT PERMITTED BY APPLICABLE LAW, NEITHER ECP NOR ANY OF ITS EMPLOYEES, OWNERS, MEMBERS, MANAGERS, PARTNERS, SPOKESPERSONS, AFFILIATES,  AGENTS,  SUPPLIERS,  SUB-CONTRACTORS OR LICENSORSMAKE ANY WARRANTIES OF ANY KIND AND DISCLAIM ALL WARRANTIES, ORAL OR WRITTEN, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, AS TO THE INFORMATION, CONTENT, MATERIALS, PRODUCTS (INCLUDING SOFTWARE) OR OTHER SERVICES INCLUDED ON OR OTHERWISE MADE AVAILABLE TO YOU THROUGH THE SITES OR ANY WARRANTIES ARISING FROM COURSE OF DEALING, COURSE OF PERFORMANCE OR OTHERWISE INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, ANY WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, CONFORMITY TO ANY REPRESENTATION OR DESCRIPTION, WARRANTIES THAT THE SITESARE COMPLETELY SECURE OR ERROR-FREE, OR WARRANTIES OF NON-INTERRUPTION, NON-INTERFERENCE OR NON-INFRINGEMENT, UNLESS OTHERWISE SPECIFIED IN WRITING.
ECP RESERVES THE RIGHT TO TERMINATE YOUR ACCESS TO THE SITES AT ANY TIME WITHOUT CAUSE OR NOTICE.
Availability of the Sites
YOU ACKNOWLEDGE THAT ACCESS TO THE SITES WILL BE PROVIDED OVER VARIOUS FACILITIES AND COMMUNICATIONS LINES, AND INFORMATION WILL BE TRANSMITTED OVER LOCAL EXCHANGE AND INTERNET BACKBONE CARRIER LINES AND THROUGH ROUTERS, SWITCHES, AND OTHER DEVICES (COLLECTIVELY, "CARRIER LINES") OWNED, MAINTAINED, AND SERVICED BY THIRD-PARTY CARRIERS, UTILITIES, AND INTERNET SERVICE PROVIDERS, ALL OF WHICH ARE BEYOND ECP’S CONTROL. ECP ASSUMES NO LIABILITY FOR OR RELATING TO THE INTEGRITY, PRIVACY, SECURITY, CONFIDENTIALITY, OR USE OF ANY INFORMATION WHILE IT IS TRANSMITTED ON THE CARRIER LINES, OR ANY DELAY,
FAILURE, INTERRUPTION, INTERCEPTION, LOSS, TRANSMISSION, OR CORRUPTION OF ANY DATA OR OTHER INFORMATION ATTRIBUTABLE TO TRANSMISSION ON THE CARRIER LINES. USE OF THE CARRIER LINES IS SOLELY AT YOUR RISK AND IS SUBJECT TO ALL APPLICABLE LOCAL, STATE, NATIONAL, AND INTERNATIONAL LAWS.
EXCEPT AS EXPRESSLY REQUIRED OR WARRANTED UNDER THE AGREEMENT AND IF, AND TO THE EXTENT, PERMITTED BY LAW, YOU AGREE THAT IN NO EVENT WILL ECP BE LIABLE FOR FAILING TO PROVIDE THE SITES UNDER ANY THEORY OF LIABILITY, WHETHER IN CONTRACT, TORT, STRICT LIABILITY OR OTHERWISE.
YOU AGREE THAT ECP TAKES NO RESPONSIBILITY FOR AND DISCLAIMS ANY AND ALL LIABILITY ARISING FROM ANY INACCURACIES OR DEFECTS IN THE COMMUNICATION LINES, THE INTERNET OR YOUR INTERNET SERVICE PROVIDER ("ISP"), COMPUTER HARDWARE OR SOFTWARE, OR ANY OTHER SERVICE OR DEVICE THAT YOU USE TO ACCESS THE SITES.
Limitation of Liability
IT IS EXPRESSLY AGREED THAT IN NO EVENT SHALL ECP BE LIABLE FOR ANY SPECIAL, INDIRECT, CONSEQUENTIAL, OR EXEMPLARY DAMAGES, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO, LOSS OF PROFITS OR REVENUES, LOSS OF USE, OR CONSISTING OF, ARISING FROM OR RELATING TO LOSS OF INFORMATION OR DATA, WHETHER A CLAIM FOR ANY SUCH LIABILITY OR DAMAGES IS PREMISED UPON BREACH OF CONTRACT, BREACH OF WARRANTY, NEGLIGENCE, STRICT LIABILITY, OR ANY OTHER THEORY OF LIABILITY, EVEN IF WE HAVE BEEN APPRISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OR LIKELIHOOD OF SUCH DAMAGES OCCURRING. WE DISCLAIM ANY AND ALL LIABILITY FOR ERRONEOUS TRANSMISSIONS AND LOSS OF SERVICE RESULTING FROM COMMUNICATION FAILURES BY TELECOMMUNICATION SERVICE PROVIDERS OR THE SITES. YOU EXPRESSLY AGREE THAT YOUR USE OF THE SITES IS AT YOUR SOLE RISK.
ECP WILL NOT BE LIABLE FOR ANY DAMAGES OF ANY KIND ARISING FROM THE USE OF ANY ECP SITE OR SERVICE, OR FROM ANY INFORMATION, CONTENT, MATERIALS, PRODUCTS (INCLUDING SOFTWARE) OR OTHER SERVICES INCLUDED ON OR OTHERWISE MADE AVAILABLE TO YOU THROUGH ANY ECP SERVICE, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, PUNITIVE, AND CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES, UNLESS OTHERWISE SPECIFIED IN WRITING.
BECAUSE SOME JURISDICTIONS DO NOT ALLOW THE EXCLUSION OR LIMITATION OF CERTAIN WARRANTIES, CONDITIONS OR CATEGORIES OF DAMAGES, CERTAIN OF THE ABOVE EXCLUSIONS OR LIMITATIONS MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU. IN SUCH JURISDICTIONS, ECP’S WARRANTIES, CONDITIONS AND LIABILITY ARE LIMITED TO THE FULLEST EXTENT PERMITTED BY LAW.
Indemnification
YOU AGREE TO INDEMNIFY, DEFEND, AND HOLD HARMLESS ECP AND OUR AFFILIATES, OFFICERS, MEMBERS, MANAGERS, OWNERS, SPOKESPERSONS, AND AGENTS, FROM AND AGAINST ANY CLAIM, COST OR LIABILITY, INCLUDING REASONABLE ATTORNEYS' FEES, ARISING OUT OF: (A) THE USE OF THE SITES BY YOU; (B) ANY BREACH BY YOU OF ANY REPRESENTATIONS, WARRANTIES OR AGREEMENTS CONTAINED IN THIS AGREEMENT; (C) THE ACTIONS OF ANY PERSON GAINING ACCESS TO THE SITES UNDER A USER ID ASSIGNED TO YOU; (D) THE ACTIONS OF ANYONE USING A USER ID, PASSWORD OR OTHER UNIQUE IDENTIFIER ASSIGNED TO YOU THAT ADVERSELY AFFECTS THE SITES OR ANY INFORMATION ACCESSED THROUGH THE SYSTEM, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO A SECURITY BREACH; AND (E) YOUR NEGLIGENT OR WILLFUL MISCONDUCT.
Restrictions on Use
YOU ACKNOWLEDGE THAT YOU ARE RESPONSIBLE FOR COMPLIANCE WITH ALL APPLICABLE, LAWS REGULATIONS AND RULES, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO LAWS, REGULATIONS OR RULES OF COUNTRIES OUTSIDE THE UNITED STATES AND WILL BEAR ANY AND ALL LIABILITY RESULTING FROM YOUR VIOLATION OF ANY SUCH RELEVANT LAW, REGULATION OR RULE, INCLUDING RELEVANT PRIVACY AND DATA PROTECTION LAWS, UNDER THE INDEMNIFICATION PROVISIONS OF THIS AGREEMENT.
Further, you agree:
You will not use the Sites for any purpose that is unlawful or prohibited by this Agreement;
You will not use the Sites to solicit the performance of any illegal activity or other activity which infringes, misappropriates or otherwise violates the rights of ECP or others;
You will not use the Sites in any manner that could damage, disable, overburden or impair any server, or the network(s) connected to any server, or interfere with any other party’s use and enjoyment of the Sites;
You will not attempt to gain unauthorized access to the Sites or any services, other accounts, computer systems or networks connected to any server or to any of the services, through hacking, password mining or any other means;
You will not obtain or attempt to obtain any materials or information not intentionally made available to you through the Sites;
You will not frame the Sites or any portion thereof without the prior written consent of ECP;
You will not use any “deep-link”, “page-scrape”, “robot”, “spider”, or other automatic device, program, algorithm or methodology, or reverse-engineer or use any similar and/or manual process, to access, acquire, catalog, store, reproduce, distribute or monitor any portion of the Sites, or in any way reproduce or circumvent the navigational structure or presentation of the Sites;
You will not take any action to interfere with, or disrupt the Sites, circumvent security measures or attempt to exceed the limited authorization and access granted to you under this Agreement;
You will not remove any copyright, trademark or other intellectual property right notices contained in the Sites; and
ECP has the right, in its sole discretion, to monitor any and all use of the Sites to the extent permitted by applicable laws, rules or regulations.
Unauthorized access to the Sites is a breach of this Agreement and may be a violation of law. You agree not to access the Sites by any means other than through the interfaces that we provide to you.
Dispute Resolution
Any controversy, claim, action or dispute arising out of or related to any transaction conducted on the Sites, or the breach, enforcement, interpretation, or validity of this Agreement or any part of it ("Dispute") may only be brought in a court of competent jurisdiction in the County of Ventura, State of California. Both you and ECP expressly agree to waive a trial by jury in any Dispute herein. You agree to submit to the personal and exclusive jurisdiction of the United States District Court in the County of Ventura, State of California. Further, both you and ECP agree that the party asserting the Dispute shall first try in good faith to settle such Dispute by providing written notice to the other party (by first class or registered mail) describing the facts and circumstances (including any relevant documentation) of the Dispute and allowing the receiving party 30 days in which to respond to or settle the Dispute. Notice shall be sent:
(1) to
ECP at:
Eurow & O’Reilly Corporation
51 Moreland Road
Simi Valley, CA 93065
(2) to you at: your last-used billing address or the billing and/or shipping address in your online profile.
Both you and ECP agree that this dispute resolution procedure is a condition precedent that must be satisfied prior to initiating any litigation or filing any claim against the other party.
YOU HEREBY KNOWINGLY AGREE THAT ANY PROCEEDING, IN COURT OR BEFORE ANY OTHER COMPETENT TRIBUNAL, INCLUDING AT ARBITRATION IF APPLICABLE, WILL BE CONDUCTED ONLY ON AN INDIVIDUAL BASIS AND NOT IN A CLASS OR REPRESENTATIVE ACTION OR AS A MEMBER IN A CLASS, CONSOLIDATED OR REPRESENTATIVE ACTION. YOU HEREBY ACKNOWLEDGE THAT BY AGREEING AND ACCEPTING THIS TERM, YOU ARE WAIVING YOUR ABILITY TO JOIN A CLASS ACTION AGAINST ECP.
Choice of Law
This Agreement shall be construed in accordance with the internal laws of the State of California, without regard to any conflict of law provisions, and the 1980 U.N. Convention on Contracts for the International Sale of Goods shall not apply. You agree to waive all defenses of personal jurisdiction and forum non conveniens with respect to venue and jurisdiction in the state or federal courts of the County of Ventura, State of California.
Miscellaneous
ECP’s failure to insist on or enforce strict performance of this Agreement shall not constitute a waiver of any provision or any right, nor shall any course of conduct between ECP and you or any other party be deemed to modify any provision of the this Agreement.
If any provision of this Agreement is found to be contrary to law or otherwise invalid or unenforceable by a court or other tribunal of competent jurisdiction, then such provision shall be limited to the minimum extent necessary to effect the order of the court or other such tribunal and construed in a way to most closely reflect the intentions of ECP and you. All other provisions shall remain in full force and effect.
Both you and ECP agree that this Agreement is the complete and exclusive statement of the mutual understanding of the Parties and supersedes and cancels all previous written, oral, or other agreements, communications, and understandings relating to the subject matter of this Agreement. Both you and ECP further agree that any waivers and modifications must be in writing and signed by both you and ECP, expect as otherwise provided in this Agreement. No agency, partnership, joint venture, employment, or other kind of relationship is created as a result of this Agreement unless expressly granted by the terms of this Agreement and you do not have any authority of any kind of bind ECP in any respect whatsoever.
Termination
These terms are effective unless and until terminated by either you or ECP. You may terminate this Agreement at any time. ECP also may terminate this Agreement at any time without notice, and accordingly may deny you access to the Sites, if in our sole judgment you fail to comply with any term or provision of the Agreement. The obligations and liabilities of you and ECP incurred prior to the termination date shall survive the termination of this Agreement for all purposes.
DMCA Notice
You acknowledge and agree that, pursuant to the Digital Millennium Copyright Act (“DMCA”), ECP may respond in accordance with the requirements of the DMCA to “take-down” notices from third parties that allege that the inclusion in or our Sites or on ECP systems of information, which you provide violates their copyrights. In so doing, ECP may elect to remove (or require you to remove) such allegedly infringing information from the Sites and/or ECP systems unless you object to the allegation of infringement, in which case ECP in its sole discretion may elect to maintain or restore the allegedly infringing information to the Website and/or ECP systems pending the outcome of litigation which you may institute against the alleged copyright owner pursuant to the DMCA. You agree to cooperate fully with ECP to assure compliance with the DMCA upon receipt by ECP of any “take-down” notice issued by any third party, and in so doing, to promptly inform ECP whether you object to any such “take-down” notice and, if so, whether you will institute litigation to challenge the allegations of copyright infringement.
Notice and Procedure for Making Claims of Copyright Infringement
ECP respects the intellectual property of others. If you believe that your work has been copied in a way that constitutes copyright infringement, please provide ECP’s copyright agent the written information specified below:
An electronic or physical signature of the person authorized to act on behalf of the owner of the copyright interest;
A description of the copyrighted work or works that you claim have been infringed upon;
A description of where the material that you claim is infringing is located on the site;
Your address, telephone number, and e-mail address;
A statement by you that you have a good faith belief that the disputed use is not authorized by the copyright owner, its agent, or the law; and
A statement by you, made under penalty of perjury, that the above information in your notice is accurate and that you are the copyright owner or authorized to act on the copyright owner's behalf.
ECP’s Copyright Agent for notice of claims of copyright infringement on the ECP Sites can be reached as follows:
Eurow & O’Reilly Corporation
51 Moreland Road
Simi Valley, CA 93065
ATTN: DMCA Copyright Agent
Email notifications may be sent to cs@equinecomfort.com
Please note that this procedure is exclusively for notifying ECP and its subsidiaries that your copyrighted material has been infringed.
Privacy Policy
Last Revised - January 4, 2017
ECP Privacy Policy
This policy describes the personal information collected by Eurow & O’Reilly Corporation (referred to as “ECP ”) on its sites, which include but are not limited to www.ECP,(the "Sites"), why we collect it, how we use it, and when we share it with third parties. The policy covers online experiences provided by ECP which includes its websites as well as its mobile sites and apps. The policy also explains the ways in which you can control how we collect and use your data.
We will update this policy from time to time, as indicated on the date posted above. However, we suggest that you review this privacy policy, at this location, regularly to review any changes that may have been made.
You may exercise your choices about how we collect and use your information consistent with this policy to the extent indicated below.
If you have any questions about our privacy policy, please contact us as described in the section entitled "How do I contact you?" below.
What types of information does ECP collect?
We may collect personal information from you, which may include:
your name
your email address
your postal address or zip-code
your phone number
your credit card number
your gender
your birthday
your personal interests
when you visit one of our websites
when you install or use our mobile sites or apps
when you place an order online or by phone
when you save your information with us online
when you contact us with a question or concern
when you participate in a contest, promotion, or survey
In addition to the above, ECP keeps records of your product interests and purchases you make online, through a mobile app or by phone. We also collect information about the device you use to access our websites, mobile sites or apps such as your computer's IP address, your browser type, your operating system, browsing information and other technical information. Our mobile sites and apps may also collect information about your location if you permit this. We may combine all of this information with information about you that we acquire from our joint marketing partners, from unrelated third parties, and from our other brands on the Sites. ECP also uses third party service providers to collect and compile this information, including Google Analytics and its Demographics and Interests features. For more information about the type of information that is gathered by Google Analytics, please visit this site.
How does ECP use my information?
ECP may use your personal information in the following ways:
To contact you if necessary;
To process and fulfill your order, including to send you emails to confirm your order status and shipment;
To help us learn more about your shopping preferences;
To help us address problems with and improve our site and mobile site and app design, products and services;
To enhance your shopping experience;
To analyze trends and statistics;
To communicate with you and to send you information by email, postal mail, telephone, text message, or other means about our products, services, contests, and promotions, unless you have directed us not to contact you with promotional communications;
To administer and fulfill our contests and other promotions; and
In other ways that are consistent with the terms of this Privacy Policy, including the section entitled “Does ECP share my information with others?”
You may always opt out of receiving calls or other marketing information. For instructions on how to opt out, please see the section entitled "How do I make choices about receiving promotional communications?" below.
Does ECP share my information with others?
We may share your personal information in the following ways:
We may share your information when we team up with another company to offer or provide products, services, contests, or promotions to our customers.
When you provide personal information to one of our ECP brands, we may share that information with our other ECP brands.
We may share information about you if necessary, in our good faith judgment and sole discretion, to comply with laws or regulations or in response to a valid subpoena, order, or government request, or to protect the rights of ECP or others.
We may share your information with our service providers who manage our customer information and perform services on our behalf, such as fulfilling promotions, sending communications to our customers, conducting surveys, etc. We do not authorize any of these service providers to make any other use or disclosure of your information.
In addition, if you choose to participate in any third-party scrip, loyalty, or similar program in which an ECP brand is a participating vendor, and you authorize ECP or our credit card processor to provide information about your purchases to the company administering the program, we will share your personal information with that program. Scrip programs allow you to instruct us to divert a percentage of the amount you spend on ECP purchases to participating schools and other non-profit organizations. Loyalty programs allow you to earn "points" on purchases at ECP brands, which you may then use toward certain rewards offered by the loyalty programs in which you participate. The information you authorize us to disclose to the third-party scrip or loyalty program may include your credit card number and the date and amount of your purchase, and may also include your name and other information you have asked us to provide. Please note that once we disclose this information, the scrip or loyalty company may use and share it with others in accordance with its own privacy policy. You should review these policies carefully, as we have no control over them.
In the event that ECP, or any of its brands, affiliates or subsidiaries is sold or merges with another company, our customers' personal information and other information collected as described in this policy may be among the transferred business assets.
How do I make choices about receiving promotional communications?
ECP wishes to communicate with you only if you want to hear from us. You may opt out of communications regarding promotional information, including special offers, deals and events by contacting us at the addresses provided in the “How do I contact you?” section below or you can use the following unsubscribe links:
When you contact customer service please provide your full name and the email account you used to register your account or made a purchase from any of the ECP sites, mobile sites or apps. If you ask us to remove your name and address from promotional lists, we will maintain your name in a "do not contact" file to ensure that we can honor your request. It may take up to 10 days to process your email request and 6-8 weeks to process your postal mail request, during which period you may continue to receive communications from ECP.
If you change your mind, you can start receiving promotional communications from us again by logging into your online account and changing your preferences, by signing up when you visit our websites or when you enter a sweepstakes or contest, or by contacting customer service.
Please note that when you make an online purchase from us, we will continue to confirm your order status and shipment by email. We may also need to contact you via telephone, email or postal mail with questions or information regarding your order.
How does ECP protect kids' privacy?
We care about the safety and privacy of children online. Pursuant to the Children’s Online Privacy Act (COPPA), we do not knowingly contact or collect personal information from children under 13. In fact, our website is not intended for children under 13 or to solicit information of any kind from children under 13.
However, it is possible that we may inadvertently receive information pertaining to children under 13. If we become aware that we have inadvertently received personal information from a visitor under the age of thirteen we will delete the information from our records. If you believe that we have received information about your child that is under the age of 13, please do not hesitate to notify us using the information in the “How do I contact you?” section below. When we receive your notification, we will delete it permanently at your request. Such notifications can be sent to: [email address]
How does ECP use cookies, pixel tags and other tracking technologies?
Our websites use "cookies," “pixel tags” and other tracking technologies, to enable functionality on our websites, including your ability to shop, as well as a variety of other ways to enhance or personalize your online browsing and shopping experience. These technologies may be used to collect information about your visit, including the pages you view, the features you use, the links you click, and other actions you take in connection with the sites and our online ads. These technologies may also be used to determine the ads you see on our sites and also on other sites.
Pixel tags in our emails may be used to track your interactions with those messages, such as when you receive, open, or click a link in an email message from us.
You have the option to set your browser not to accept cookies or to notify you when you are sent a cookie, giving you the opportunity to decide whether or not to accept it. If you do not accept cookies, however, you may not be able to access your account information or make purchases on our websites.
We may combine the information we collect through these technologies with other information we have collected from and about you and use it as described in this policy.
We use cookies we set to help determine which of our ads are shown to you on other websites. To opt out of this targeted online advertising by ECP that utilizes our cookies, please click [link to cookie / pixel tracking disable page].
We also work with third-party companies that use their tracking technologies (including cookies and pixel tags) on our websites in order to provide tailored advertisements on our behalf and on behalf of other advertisers across the Internet. These companies may collect information about your activity on our sites and your interaction with our advertising and other communications and use this information to determine which ads you see on third-party websites and applications. For more information about this practice and to understand your options including how to opt out of receiving these tailored advertisements, please visit http://www.aboutads.info.
Please note that even if you opt-out, these tracking technologies may still collect data and you will still see ads, but they will not be targeted based upon the information collected through these tracking technologies.
How do I contact you?
For questions regarding this privacy policy, to opt out of receiving promotional communications, to update or change personal information or to place an order, you can contact us at:
Eurow & O’Reilly Corporation
51 Moreland Road
Simi Valley, CA 93065
Phone: (877) 580-9735
cs@equinecomfort.com
Your California Privacy Rights
California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits customers of ECP who are California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. Under California law, California residents are entitled to ask us for a notice identifying the categories of personal customer information that we share with our affiliates and/or third parties for marketing purposes, and provide contact information for such affiliates and/or third parties. If you are a California resident and would like a copy of this notice, please submit a written request to:
Eurow & O’Reilly Corporation
51 Moreland Road
Simi Valley, CA 93065
Phone: (877) 580-9735
cs@equinecomfort.com
Do Not Track
While many current browsers permit you to send a signal to us about your Do Not Track (“DNT”) preferences, we do not respond to DNT signals sent from your browser.
International Users
ECP makes no claims that user content uploaded may be appropriately protected pursuant to privacy and data protection laws outside of the United States. Users from outside the United States, including the European Union, are advised that ECP stores personal information on servers within the United States, and they are further advised that personal information uploaded to the Sites may not be protected in accordance with their local laws and regulations. If you upload personal information to the Sites from outside the United States, you do so at your own risk.  ECP is not responsible for compliance with the laws of your jurisdiction and makes no representations, warranties or guarantees that it complies with privacy, data protection or cyber security laws and regulations outside the United States.
